http://allfoodequipment.naphix.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - ALL FOOD EQUIPMENT
1300 400 555 Login Quote (0)
HomeWhy Buy From UsNewsFinanceQuick-LinksAbout UsOur ClientsSuppliers Spare PartsDeliveryTerms & ConditionsReturnsPrivacy PolicyFAQsContact
View all results Privacy Policy Home
Privacy PolicyGENERALPrivacy Policy for allfoodequipment.com.au owned and operated by All Food Equipment. Thank you for taking the time to learn more about how All Food Equipment manages your personal information.This Privacy Policy explains All Food Equipment’s privacy practices in relation to its Internet web sites allfoodequipment.com.au (“Site”). In some cases this Site may link or refer you to other web sites or organisations, which have their own privacy policy and practices.In this Privacy Policy, when we refer to ‘personal information’, we mean information that can identify you or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained – for example, your name and contact details. By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.We reserve the right, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and this Privacy Policy should be read with the other terms and conditions applicable to the use of this Site (See the Site’s Terms of Use).PERSONAL INFORMATIONYou can use this Site without telling us who you are. The only personal information we collect about you is that which you choose to tell us. For example, we may need to collect your personal information so that we can provide you with services or to answer or forward your request enquiriesiries. It is our intention that this Privacy Policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia.HOW INFORMATION IS USEDPersonal information that visitors submit to this Site is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we tell you otherwise in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Certain information you submit to this Site (for example, through the “sign up to our mailing list” feature) is sent to us over the internet, and used by our staff to contact you with regard to your enquiry. This information is not used by us for any other purpose.DISCLOSUREApart from where you have consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information may be disclosed in special situations where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with All Food Equipment’s rights or property, users of this Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, we may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure.SECURITYWe strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our Site, and we review and update our security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. We will nonetheless endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us.In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.COOKIESA cookie is a very small text file that is sent to a user’s browser from a web server and stored on the user’s computer hard drive. Cookies save you time because they help us to provide a customized experience without having to remind us of your preferences each time you return to our web pages. The allfoodequipment.com.au cookies cannot damage files, nor can they read information from the hard drive of a computer.Cookies can help us provide our visitors with a personalized online experience in the following ways: • They remember names and passwords for future visits so log-in is easier and faster • They ensure visitors are provided with the appropriate frames and content • They ensure visitors obtain the information requested • They help us deliver communications that are relevant and targeted to our visitors’ interestsThe allfoodequipment.com.au cookies do not follow visitors when travelling on the Internet after leaving the allfoodequipment.com.au site. We track the usage of our site in order to modify it according to our visitors’ needs. We pay attention to what information is requested and attempt to make it easier to find such information in the future.If visitors do not want the benefits of these cookies they can set their browser to reject the cookies. Visitors should consult the instructions for their particular browser on how to do this. However, visitors should understand that rejecting cookies might affect their ability to perform certain transactions on our site and our ability to recognise their browser from one visit to the next.SITE LOGSLike many web site operators, we also use software to analyse and record visitor numbers and other details such as: the number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on Site; the number of visitors to our Site; how long those visitors (on average) spend on our Site when they do visit; and common entry and exit points into our Site. This aggregate, non-personal information is used by us to assist in analysing the usage of our web site.ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep any information that we hold about you accurate and up to date. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect or if you otherwise wish to review or correct that information, please contact us.LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITESWe may provide links from this Site to other web sites (“linked sites”). Unless we tell you otherwise, these linked sites are not under our control, and we do not accept responsibility for the privacy practices of those sites or their operators. Before disclosing your personal information to any other web site, you should examine the terms and conditions of those sites and their privacy practices.CORRECTING OR UPDATING YOUR INFORMATIONIf you would like to correct or update your user name, email address or any other details you should contact the privacy officer. For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy, visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner’s website at www.privacy.gov.au.PLEASE TELL US WHAT YOU THINKAll Food Equipment welcomes your questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any suggestions as to how we may improve our privacy practices or if you have reason to believe that this Policy has not been complied with, we urge you to let us know. Our contact details are as follows:Attention: All Food Equipment Ph: 1300 400 555 Email: enquiry@allfoodequipment.com.auAll ProductsCurrent SpecialsBAKERY EQUIPMENTBread SlicersDough RollersDough SheetersFood Displays >ColdFood Displays >HotPlanetary MixersProofersSpiral MixersBLENDERSBar Drink BlendersStick BlendersTilting BlendersCATERING EQUIPMENTAuto Boil Water UnitsBain MariesBlender MixersBoiling PlatesBone SawsCheese GratersChilled Drink DispensersChip WarmersChocolate MelterCoffee Espresso MachinesCoffee PercolatorsConvection OvensConveyor ToastersCream Gun WhippersCrepe MakersDeep FryersExhaust Canopy HoodsFood Cutting MixersFood Holding & DisplayFood ProcessorsFry Stations & Multi ProductHeat LampsHeated CabinetHot Dog MachinesHot Food WellHot Water UrnsJuice ExtractorsMeat MincersMeat SlicersMicrowavesMilkshake MixersPeelersPie WarmersPlate DispensersPlate WarmersRice Cookers / WarmersSausage FillersSoup WarmersSteamersStick Hand BlendersThermometers >FoodThermometers >MilkToastersVacuum Pack SealersVacuum Sealer BagsVegetable SlicersWaffle MakersWarming DrawersWedgers / ChoppersCOFFEE EQUIPMENTBoiling Water UnitsCoffee Bean GrindersCoffee BrewersCoffee Deli GrindersCoffee DispensersCoffee PercolatorsCream WhippersEspresso Coffee MachinesHot Water UrnsMilk Frothing JugsMilk ThermometersTraining BooksWaste TubesCOOKING EQUIPMENTBain Maries >ElectricBoiling Hot PlatesBoiling PansBraising PansBratt Pans >ElectricBratt Pans >GasChar Broiler BBQ GrillsCharcoal Meat BBQ'sChicken RotisseriesChip WarmersCook Top RangesCrepe Maker MachinesDeep FryersDoner Kebab MachinesGriddles >ElectricGriddles >GasGriddles >ToastersInduction CooktopsMicrowave OvensOven RangesOvens >Combi-SteamOvens >ConvectionOvens >ConveyorOvens >Electric Baking OvenPasta CookersPie WarmersPizza Conveyor OvensPizza Deck OvensRice CookersSalamandersSoup KettlesSteam Combi OvensTarget Boiling TopsToaster >ContactToaster >ConveyorsToastersWaffle MakersWok BurnersCurrent SpecialsDISHWASHERS & GLASSWASHERDishwashers - UndercounterPass Through DishwashersPass Through Glass WashersUnderbench GlasswashersDRINK DISPENSERSCold Drink DispensersGranita - Slushie MachinesIce Filled Drink DispensersSlushie SyrupsFAIRY FLOSS EQUIPMENTFairy Floss MachinesUsable ProductsFLOOR SAFETY MATSKItchen Floor MatsFOOD DISPLAY CABINETSBar Display FridgesBench-top Glass FridgesCake Fridges >Bench-topCake Fridges >UprightChocolate casesFood Displays >AmbientFood Displays >ColdFood Displays >HotGlass 1 Door FridgesGlass 2 Door FridgesGlass 3 Door FridgesPie WarmersSelf-Service Bars >ColdSelf-Service Bars >HotSushi Display FridgesFREEZERSBar FreezersBench FreezersBlast FreezersChest Display FreezersChest Storage FreezersCounter-top FreezersFreezer Storage RoomsGelato / Ice Cream FreezersGlass 1 Door FreezersGlass 2 Door FreezersGlass 3 Door FreezersStorage 1 Door FreezersStorage 2 Door FreezersStorage 3 Door FreezersFRIDGESBack Bar FridgesBar FridgesBench Fridges >Glass-DoorsBench Fridges >Solid-DoorsBlast ChillersCake Fridges >Counter-topsCake Fridges >Floor ModelsCold Food DisplaysCool RoomsCounter-top FridgesDelicatessen DisplaysGlass 1 Door Display FridgesGlass 2 Door Display FridgesGlass 3 Door Display FridgesMedical RefrigerationOpen Reach-In DisplaysPizza & Sandwich Bench-Top FridgesPizza Prep FridgesSandwich Bench FridgesSelf Service Cold BarsStorage 1 Door FridgesStorage 2 Door FridgesStorage 3 Door FridgesSushi Display FridgesWine Storage FridgesHAND DRYERSWashroom Hand DryersICE CUBE MAKERSIce Makers to 40kgIce Makers to 70kgIce Makers upto -145kgIce Makers upto -395kgIce Makers upto 1100kgIce Makers with Drain PumpsWater Filters for Ice MakersICE DISPENSERSAuto Ice Maker DispensersJUICING EQUIPMENTCitrus SqueezersFruit & Vegetable JuicersJuice / Drink DispensersOrange / Fruit PeelersOrange Auto JuicersWheat-Grass JuicersPOPCORN EQUIPMENTPopcorn ConsumablesPopcorn MachinesPopcorn WarmersSNOW CONE EQUIPMENTSno-Cone CupsSnow Cone CartsSnow Cone MachinesSnow Cone SyrupsSTAINLESS PRODUCTSBenches >1 Sink BowlBenches >2 Sink BowlBenches >3 Sink BowlBenches >DishwashersBenches >KitchenBenches >SalamanderExhaust HoodsFront Service CountersGastronorm Food PansHand Sanitizer DispenserHand Wash StationPre-Rinse Spray ArmsShelves >Pipe/PotShelves >WallTrolleys >GastronormTrolleys >ServingWashing SinksUncategorisedWhy choose All Food Equipment? Lowest Price GuaranteeIt's unlikely, but if you happen to get a cheaper quoted price for the same equipment model we’ll match or beat it!* Our price guarantee Fast & Free QuotesJust select equipment - add your details and we'll get back to you quickly with an amazing deal. How quotes work Flexible FinanceWe know that setting up or renovating can be expensive. We are here to help with rental and purchasing options. Our finance options $20000 Tax Deduction For New EquipmentGreat news for all Australian small businesses are now eligible to a 100% Tax deduction on new... View News ArticleQuicklinksAbout UsOur ClientsSuppliers Spare PartsFAQsTerms & ConditionsNewsFinanceCommon FAQ’sQ: How do I get a Free Quote?Q: Are your products 100% Genuine?Q: Can I open a Credit account?Q: Do you have a Showroom?Q: Can I pick up my order?Q: Do you sell Used Equipment?Q: Is your website secure? Subscribe and FollowWant to get great news and be in the loop for all our monthly specials? Just enter your details below!**
© 2020 Wefix Pty Ltd T/A ALL FOOD EQUIPMENT.site secured byTerms & ConditionsSitemap
